Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Are you saying you're not
mad at me anymore?
This is the first time
that you'll attend
the birthday celebration of the
Governor General.
Miss Carmelita...
Do not dance provocatively!
Oops!
Miss Carmelita...
May I dance the Cariñosa with you?
Trinidad's family was murdered?
I promised Trinidad and Nestor...
That I will not stop until I discover
who had them murdered.
How can you murder
Trinidad's whole family?
I didn't expect my own daughter
to believe the lies made
to ruin her Father's reputation.
The one who will kill Juanito,
is it still the same person?
I'm sure it's still the same people.
People? So there's more than one?
You must also ensure
the safety of the Montecarlos family.
Oh no! I can't fall in
love with Juanito. I can't!
Carmelita is the one destined for Juanito.
But I am the one Juanito met.
I mean... this is still my body.
I'm still me, the original Carmela.
How about Helena?
Should I ask Juanito
if he still likes Helena?
But I can't!
No. I can't.
Should I still push Juanito
and Helena for each other?
I also can't do that. I
mean, how about Carmelita?
I mean... how about me?
No, that's not important. You know what?
What's more important
is how Juanito found
out about my real name?
Did Mother Olivia tell him?
Let go of me.
Miss, what are you doing here?
Why are you drinking alcohol?
What's it to you if I want to get drunk?
I don't care if you tell my Daddy
or cut my allowance, go ahead!
What are you talking about?
Hey, wait! That's mine.
Did you drink all my wine?
You drank all my wine!
- Miss. That's enough.
- No! Give me that!
Give me wine! Give me more wine!
- I want more wine! Give me more--
- Miss!
Be quiet!
You'll get reprimanded and
punished by Mother Olivia.
Ouch!
Miss Carmelita, let's go.
I don't want to.
- Miss, come. I'll take you to your room.
- I said I don't want to!
- Miss! Miss, please don't!
- Daddy! Daddy, help me!
Miss Carmelita, please don't be too loud.
Okay, I won't be loud.
Quiet, shh...
Miss, you are too drunk. You need to rest.
Come, let's go.
- I said no!
- But Miss...
Miss Carmelita, you need
to get some rest. You--
I am not Carmelita.
So don't call me Carmelita.
Miss Carmelita, you are very drunk. Come.
I'll assist you.
I'll take you to your room...
I said I'm not Carmelita!
I am a humble impostor!
Ouch!
Alright, fine.
You're not Miss Carmelita.
Then who are you?
Me? I'm Carmela.
I think this is some sort of punishment.
Because some people say I'm mean
and always gets into fights.
I always disagree with my Dad and siblings.
Carmelita, on the other hand...
She's nice and respectful...
She always gets praised by Doña Soledad
and Don Alejandro.
But...
It's so exhausting being her.
I need to be mindful of her reputation.
Are you saying you're Carmelita
when you're acting refined
around your parents?
And you're Carmela
when you're easy-going
whenever you're around me?
It's kind of like that but not really.
You should... learn to know
the differences between them.
Who do you like better?
If I had to choose...
I like you when you're Carmela because...
Good thing Juanito
misunderstood the whole thing.
He thinks that I'm talking
about different personas.
He didn't realize that Carmelita and
Carmela are literally two different people.
Carmelita, Juanito sent a letter for you.
Miss Carmelita, I would like to invite you
to an important trip tomorrow.
- Mr. Pipoy.
- Good morning, Juanito.
Do you have news of my wife?
I asked my Father for help.
The search continues even
without news of her whereabouts.
Ladies, this is Mr. Pipoy
Sergio introduced me to him a few days ago.
My brother is helping
me with my investigation.
What are you investigating?
Aside from searching
for Mr. Pipoy's wife...
I'm also shedding light
to the truth behind the
murder of Trinidad's family.
This woman is named Cristeta.
She's the daughter of Trinidad and Nestor.
I've just finished cleaning headstones...
When I saw her crying and wounded.
That is why I took her home.
Cristeta, how did you survive?
After putting sacks over us,
they took us to a secluded place...
A man was supposed to shoot me.
But a man wearing black suddenly came.
He said...
I'm safe.
In return, I have to say that Don
Alejandro was the mastermind.
I cannot do it.
I don't want a family to
be ruined because of a lie.
Cristeta...
Cristeta?
Are you alright?
- Cristeta!
- What's happening to you?
Write a letter of apology to Father.
And if it's alright with you,
I'll accompany Mr. Pipoy
in taking Cristeta home.
I also want to pray for her family.
- Cristeta, come on, let's go.
- Cristeta...
Come.
So you can ease your worries.
We're going somewhere.
What are we even doing here?
Isn't reading books one of your hobbies?
Oh, I forgot that in
this era I'm Carmelita,
a certified bookworm.
There's something I want you to read.
To me?
I think...
I'm feeling dizzy.
You know, I think I won't be able to read
for a few months...
If you need someone to
read for you, I am here.
Don't you worry.
Why do you always say that
you're gonna be there for me?
That's not true.
You can't accompany
me to every single thing.
And there's no such thing as forever.
I mean... nothing lasts forever.
I can take care of myself.
Look at my muscles.
You really don't
have to be alone.
Because I'd like to be with you.
Because I'm happy when we're together.
Oh, really?
Don't look for another book.
Here is the greatest book.
A collection of songs,
poems, and short stories.
All about love.
Alright, fine.
Why do you want to read
a book about love anyway?
You know what I'm
interested in? Things like...
Violence. Shows full of action.
Shows?
Do you mean to say... theater plays?
Yes?
If that's the case... this Sunday, I'll
ask permission from Mother Olivia.
Let's go to the theater.
I am yours and you are mine.
That is what's written in the stars.
Clouds may cover the skies.
But no one can ever stop us.
In the rising and setting of the sun.
You are what I dream of.
In the midst of hunger and thirst.
You are what I crave for.
The promise that I swore to you.
to never leave you.
Rest assured, my heart is steadfast.
My love for you is more than enough.
Beautiful. That was beautiful.
How about you, Miss? What
is your favorite poem or story?
I forgot the title, but...
It's about a lady who was
supposed to marry a prince.
But she was pushed into a deep well.
And got transported into another world.
There, she met a gentleman.
And she slowly fell in love with him.
But when the prince who was engaged to her
suddenly came...
The lady realized that...
Her heart now belongs to somebody else.
What happened in the end?
Did they end up together?
Yeah, but...
It's just a show, anyway.
They can't be together in real life.
They're from different worlds.
They're not for each other.
Is someone there?
Do you still feel unwell?
I can handle it.
But you're upset.
I was just thinking...
Why Juanito didn't even visit me?
How will he?
He and Carmelita were together in the
Governor-General's party a few days ago.
Seems like something's
going on between them.
Save your strength.
Prepare yourself for a battle.
Who's there?
Mr. Valdez.
What are you doing here? And...
Why are you alone together?
- We're not doing anything wrong!
- You're misunderstanding this.
You are...
Carmelita?
The daughter of Don Alejandro Montecarlos?
You were but a child when I last saw you.
I am Valentino Valdez.
An old friend and former lawyer
of your departed grandfather,
Don Santiago.
Ahh...
Well then, don't you worry.
I will just say that I am
with you here in the library.
And there's nothing wrong with that since
you are about to get married.
In February, isn't it?
Your mother sent me an invitation.
Why did you return so late?
What happened to you?
Why is your face so flushed?
I'll go inside.
Good evening, Mother Olivia.
Shocks. Juanito is my first kiss.
Don't overreact. It's nothing.
Our lips just accidentally
touched. That's it!
I need to get this out of my head.
Wait...
I have to write a letter to Don Alejandro.
Dear Father, I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
That's it.
I'll explain it ASAP.
Bye.
Tc.
Ily.
Imy.
More loves, Carmelita.
Your things. You forgot
it in Mother Olivia's room.
Where did you and Juanito go to last night
and why were you together?
Wait, why would I let
myself be bullied by this girl?
Why not?
What did you say?
Easy, Carmela. Don't give
yourself more problems.
Why don't we eat and pray?
They're surely waiting
for us. I'll go ahead.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with you.
Blessed are you among women,
Lord God.
Did you know how many times
I tried to stay away from Juanito.
Guide my heart. I
don't want to fall for him.
Now and at the hour of our death. Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with you.
Blessed are you among women,
and blessed is the fruit
of your womb, Jesus..
Holy Mary, mother of God --
Josefina! Josefina! Bring her to her room!
Josefina! Take some rest.
Quickly.
Mother Olivia...
Are you also not feeling well?
Don't worry about me.
I just didn't get enough sleep last night.
Call a doctor.
Maybe Doctor Hidalgo, is he available?
He went to Paris last week.
What do we do?
There isn't a doctor
who could check Josefina
How about Juanito?
He's studying medicine.
Maybe he can check Josefina?
He's not a licensed doctor, Carmelita.
Will you risk your sister's life like that?
Josefina has a very high fever.
It was Josefina who gave
Helena her food last night.
Is it possible she caught
Helena's disease too?
Juanito... could you also
check my sister, Helena?
Carmelita.
I just want to know my sister's
condition. Please do not worry.
Helena also needs Juanito's help.
Sure.
Doctor Ramiro already saw Helena yesterday.
He said Helena's already better
and doesn't need to take medication.
Thank you, dear boy. For all your help.
- Go home and take some rest.
- Yes, Mother Olivia.
Oh, by the way.
Mr. Juanito.
Please prescribe the
medicines Josefina needs to take.
Give it to Carmelita.
Me?
Ladies...
Ignacio.
Juanito.
How's Josefina doing?
Her fever's quite high.
How about Carmelita?
Did you talk to her?
No.
But I left a letter for her.
Carmelita, will you let me
take care of Josefina for now?
I want to pay back the
kindness she has given me.
Of course.
Juanito gave a list of what
Josefina may or may not eat.
And also the medicines she must take.
The list is over there.
Don't worry.
I'll do my best so Josefina
can recover quickly.
I'll go ahead.
Carmelita!
Did Juanito gave you a letter for me?
He hasn't sent me any letters
since he came back here in Manila.
Maybe... he just got busy with his studies.
He has always been busy,
but has never forgotten to write to me.
Isn't it very strict in here as well?
Letters couldn't pass through easily,
maybe that's why you haven't received it.
Also, everyone knows we're engaged.
People might misunderstand.
I understand.
I am willing to wait.
I apologize for acting worried,
but believe me, I don't
have doubts about you.
I can see that you don't
have any feelings for Juanito.
And I also know how true your
love is for my brother, Leandro
Am I right?
Of course.
I'll go ahead, okay?
Let's meet at Plaza Santo
Tomas tomorrow afternoon.
I already asked Mother Olivia and she gave
her permission for us to go to the theater.
This Sunday, I'll ask
permission from Mother Olivia.
Let's go to the theater.
I'm sure you'll like the
performances this weekend.
I don't know where
and what time we'll meet.
But I think he'll fetch me here?
Surely he'll come here.
Oh no! I don't have that much
accessories here in the dormitory.
I'll just wear this then.
I'm sure I'll be prettier.
Don't worry. I have an errand of my own.
Why do I feel a little guilty?
Carmelita. The one waiting
for you outside is too handsome!
You're such a lucky girl, Carmelita!
Oh wow, don't tell me
you're interested in him too?
I'm warning you.
Of course not!
Alright. I'll go ahead.
Good afternoon... Carmelita.
Where is Juanito?
What are you doing here?
I feel like melting just from his stare.
I wanted to surprise you.
Apologies if I didn't
inform you of my plan.
But... do not worry.
Mother Olivia gave me
permission for us to go outside.
Gosh... #FeelingBetrayed.
It's so pretty in here, don't you think?
Just as pretty as you, my love.
So they call each other "my love."
Carmelita! Mr. Leandro.
- Leandro.
- Ignacio.
Miss Sonya.
What is this? A triple date?
Why is Juanito looking at me so sourly?
Did he join Natasha in the
Skin-Carmela-Alive Club?
Why didn't you tell me that
you were going out as well?
Welcome back, Mr. Leandro.
I heard of your return just a few days ago.
I meant for my arrival to be a surprise
just for my beloved Carmelita.
Is this the first time you saw
one another in seven months?
We saw each other a week ago
when I returned to San Alfonso.
Gosh! Sonya knows about
Carmelita and Leandro's relationship.
I knew it.
That's why you didn't
travel with us to Manila.
It's because you're
waiting for Mr. Leandro.
Helena. You're brother is back now.
Yes.
Natasha and Helena
visited me earlier today.
So, she knew that Leandro
was the one waiting for me.
And why is she with Juanito anyway?
I wasn't planning on meeting Carmelita yet.
But according to Helena...
My love has been yearning for me.
He called me "my love" in front of Juanito!
He's so nonchalant about it.
What are you even expecting, Carmela?
Here's to your homecoming, Mr. Leandro.
Thank you very much, Mr. Ignacio.
I also want to extend my warm
congratulations to your wedding.
Mr. Juanito Alfonso.
It's a pleasure meeting you again.
And the pleasure's mine as well, Leandro.
Do you know my brother, Juanito?
We were classmates in our
elementary painting class.
Juanito, do you still paint?
Why does he keep glancing at me?
Not anymore.
My interest in painting already faded.
It's funny to think how big Manila is,
but for some reason, you went here too.
My loving husband has been
meaning to take me here for quite awhile.
On the way here, we saw Helena
and Juanito at the Plaza Santo Tomas.
My God, we also didn't know that
they're secretly meeting each other.
Ouch! Why did my heart hurt a little bit?
Very well. Let us continue eating.
My love... just look at them.
I hope we're as sweet as
them once we get married.
Apologies for my behavior.
Don't you worry about it, Leandro.
We're used to Carmelita's
flirtatious side once in a while.
OMG! So Carmelita has a naughty side too!
That explains why Leandro
is so aggressive towards me
since he knows Carmelita is a flirt too.
My love... slow down in
eating. You might choke.
Wait a minute!
Who gave you this ring?
I'm the one who gave her that ring.
It symbolizes my promise
to never be parted with her ever again.
And that I will love her for eternity.
Why did I wear this ring today?!
Helena, make sure you eat a lot.
Don't mind them, Carmela.
You'll just stress yourself.
Helena, when will you say yes to Juanito?
The truth is, I really want him to be...
Carmelita?
- Water...
- Carmelita?
Here, drink.
Carmelita?
Carmelita, are you okay?
So that's why my date
with Juanito didn't happen.
Because he has another date.
Carmelita?
Let me tell you the story
even though you're sleeping.
I can't contain this happiness
within me any longer.
I hope,
I'll end up with the man
I'm with right now.
You don't need to hide.
Because no matter where you are,
I will always find you.
You love painting, don't you?
You told me
it's imposible
for a person's interest
to truly disappear.
Then how about you?
Before that,
I want to give you something.
I hope you'll like it.
What is this for?
Helena!
Juanito...
Marry me...
Don't bother
writing to my Father.
I will deliver the message myself.
So that he'll know
that his daughter regained her clarity.